<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<pages>
  <OurAmbassadors>
    <heading>Our Ambassadors</heading>
    <img src="Resources/images/WhatWeDo/OurAmbassadors.png" />
    <content>The Child Cancer Foundation is incredibly grateful for the wonderful support and work our ambassadors do for the Foundation who range form athletes to radio personalities. Continue down the page to find out who these terrific people are.

      Steve Price
      Bernadine Olver-Kerby
      Lorraine Downes
      Amanda Billing
      Megan Alatini
      Jerome Kaino
      Chris Jack
      Kieran Read
      Hamish Bond and Eric Murray
    </content>
  </OurAmbassadors>

  <HowWeHelp>
    <heading>How We Help</heading>
    <img src="Resources/images/WhatWeDo/HowWeHelp.jpg" />
    <content>The Child Cancer Foundation helps the children and their families who are walking down the child cancer path in numerous ways. These services are:

      Family Support Coordinators
      Volunteer Branches
      Health Professionals
      Support Programmes
      Scholarship Programme
      Beads of Courage®
      Sharing Magazine
      Family Places
      Holiday Homes
    </content>
  </HowWeHelp>

  <AboutUs>
    <heading>About Us</heading>
    <img src="Resources/images/WhatWeDo/AboutUs.jpg" />
    <content>
Every week in New Zealand three families are told their child has cancer. We support these families from the very beginning.  Our vision is that every child and their family walking the child cancer journey will never feel alone and our mission is to support them throughout their journey.

By doing this we reduce isolation and the impact of cancer. Through offering and coordinating support services we ensure children and their families are supported, informed, and well cared for at every stage of their cancer journey.

The Foundation’s work with children with cancer and their families is unique and receives no direct government funding or support from other cancer agencies.
    </content>
  </AboutUs>

  <OurStories>
    <heading>Our Stories</heading>
    <img src="Resources/images/WhatWeDo/OurStories.jpg" />
    <content>
      <b>Claudia Little... Look at her now!</b>

Claudia is now seven and finished treatment for Wilms Tumour in January 2011.

She was diagnosed in June 2009.  Claudia was lucky enough to be able to start school on her fifth birthday which was only one month after she finished treatment.

She attends Our Lady Star of the Sea School in Howick and is now in Year Three.  Claudia enjoys doing gym, jazz dancing, and swimming.  She has won lots of medals in her gym competitions this year.  She also loves attending the camps run by Camp Quality.  She loves school and has great friends.

Claudia in 2010 as one of our ambassadors.

<b>Dequarn Harrison.. Look at him now!</b>

Dequarn is now five and started school at the beginning of the year at Pukekohe Hill Primary.

Dequarn was diagnosed with Acute Lymphoblastic Leukaemia in 2009 and completed treatment in February this year.

Dequarn loves everything about school - the kids, the environment - and is always happy to go.  He particularly enjoys physical education, and was relieved to have his portacath removed earlier this year.  Before treatment Dequarn, who is of Maori and Cook Island heritage, used to have long curly hair worn in a plait. These days he is sporting a Mohawk!

Dequarn as one of our 2011 ambassadors
      
<b>Joyce Singh... Look at her now! </b>

Joyce was diagnosed with Acute Lymphoblastic Leukaemia in November 2009 and finished treatment in March this year.

She is now enjoying going to school at Valley School in Pukekohe where she enjoys sports, maths and reading.

Joyce’s big passion is now karate, which she got into after her best friend took it up. She enjoys the moves and learning how to defend herself.  Joyce loved doing TV work when she was an ambassador for CCF and wanted to be a model. She has changed her mind now though. She doesn’t want to model, but would still like to be on TV as a presenter one day.

Joyce as one of our 2011 ambassadors

    </content>
  </OurStories>

  <OurHistory>
    <heading>Our History</heading>
    <img src="Resources/images/WhatWeDo/OurHistory.jpg" />
    <content>
In 1978 a group of concerned parents together with health professionals, formed a small Auckland based committee looking at the special needs of children with cancer and their families.

From the small beginning, dedicated people established what is now a national organization which is made up of 6 regions Northern, Waikato, Mid-Northern, Central, Canterbury/West Coast and Otago Southland.  These regions support 22 branches around the country.
    </content>
  </OurHistory>

  <OurPeople>
    <heading>Our People</heading>
    <img src="Resources/images/WhatWeDo/OurPeople.png" />
    <content>      Maryanne Thomson
        National Manager - Child Cancer Services
        PHN 09 303 9888
        EML mthomson@childcancer.org.nz
        
      Marie Purcell
        Family Support Manager - Auckland / Northland
        PHN 09 303 9977
        EML mpurcell@childcancer.org.nz
      </content>
  </OurPeople>

  <HealthProfessionals>
    <heading>Health Professionals</heading>
    <img src="Resources/images/WhatWeDo/HealthProfessionals.jpg" />
    <content>
      The Foundation works alongside the health professionals to encourage further research and education to ensure that every New Zealand child facing cancer has the best possible outcome. In recent years, the Foundation has also contributed towards research into the late effects of cancer treatment.
    </content>
  </HealthProfessionals>
</pages>