<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<pages>
  <OurAmbassadors>
    <heading>Our Ambassadors</heading>
    <img src="Resources/images/WhatWeDo/OurAmbassadors.png" />
    <content>The Child Cancer Foundation is incredibly grateful for the wonderful support and work our ambassadors do for the Foundation who range from athletes to radio personalities. These wonderful people are:

      • Steve Price
      • Bernadine Olver-Kerby
      • Lorraine Downes
      • Amanda Billing
      • Megan Alatini
      • Jerome Kaino
      • Chris Jack
      • Kieran Read
      • Hamish Bond and Eric Murray
    </content>
  </OurAmbassadors>

  <HowWeHelp>
    <heading>How We Help</heading>
    <img src="Resources/images/WhatWeDo/HowWeHelp.jpg" />
    <content>The Child Cancer Foundation helps the children and their families who are walking down the child cancer path in numerous ways. Our services include:

      • Family Support Coordinators
      • Volunteer Branches
      • Health Professionals
      • Support Programmes
      • Scholarship Programme
      • Beads of Courage®
      • Sharing Magazine
      • Family Places
      • Holiday Homes
    </content>
  </HowWeHelp>

  <AboutUs>
    <heading>About Us</heading>
    <img src="Resources/images/WhatWeDo/AboutUs.jpg" />
    <content>
Every week in New Zealand three families are told their child has cancer. We support these families from the very beginning.  Our vision is that every child and their family walking the child cancer journey will never feel alone and our mission is to support them throughout their journey.

By doing this we reduce isolation and the impact of cancer. Through offering and coordinating support services we ensure children and their families are supported, informed, and well cared for at every stage of their cancer journey.

The Foundation’s work with children with cancer and their families is unique and receives no direct government funding or support from other cancer agencies.
    </content>
  </AboutUs>

  <OurHistory>
    <heading>Our History</heading>
    <img src="Resources/images/WhatWeDo/OurHistory.jpg" />
    <content>
In 1978 a group of concerned parents together with health professionals, formed a small Auckland based committee looking at the special needs of children with cancer and their families.

From the small beginning, dedicated people established what is now a national organization which is made up of 6 regions Northern, Waikato, Mid-Northern, Central, Canterbury/West Coast and Otago Southland.  These regions support 22 branches around the country.
    </content>
  </OurHistory>

  <OurPeople>
    <heading>Our People</heading>
    <img src="Resources/images/WhatWeDo/OurPeople.png" />
    <content>National Manager (Child Cancer Services)
      Maryanne Thomson
      (09) 303 9888
      mthomson@childcancer.org.nz

Family Support Manager (Auckland / Northland)
      Marie Purcell
      (09) 303 9977
      mpurcell@childcancer.org.nz
    </content>
  </OurPeople>

  <HealthProfessionals>
    <heading>Health Professionals</heading>
    <img src="Resources/images/WhatWeDo/HealthProfessionals.jpg" />
    <content>The Foundation works alongside the health professionals to encourage further research and education to ensure that every New Zealand child facing cancer has the best possible outcome. In recent years, the Foundation has also contributed towards research into the late effects of cancer treatment.
    </content>
  </HealthProfessionals>
</pages>