<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<pages>
  <Scholarships>
    <heading>Scholarships</heading>
    <content>Child Cancer Foundation Scholarship Fund aims to assist children aged 0 to 12 years with cancer, their siblings aged 0 to 12 years, or parents, achieve their personal education and developmental goals. Any activity that has the potential to educationally or developmentally benefit the applicant will be considered.

The Scholarship sub-committee, which meets four times a year, receives and considers all applications. Allocations made depend on the funds available and are made according to the policy guidelines of the Child Cancer Foundation.

Application forms can be found on our website: www.childcancer.org.nz
    </content>
  </Scholarships>

  <SharingMagazine>
    <heading>Sharing magazine</heading>
    <img src="Resources/sharing_magazine.jpg" />
    <content>Sharing is a magazine for families, members and friends of the Foundation. It is published three times annually and includes family stories, news and Child Cancer Foundation family activities.
    </content>
  </SharingMagazine>

  <HolidayHomes>
    <heading>Holiday homes</heading>
    <img src="Resources/holiday_home.jpg" />
    <content>Child Cancer Foundation has three holiday homes available to our children with cancer and their families. We have homes in Taupo, Arrowtown and Hawkes Bay. All our houses can be booked rent free for one week. The homes are well-resourced and provide families with the opportunity to spend time together in a relaxing setting.

Long months of treatment can take a significant financial and emotional toll on families, and finding funds for a much-needed holiday can be very difficult. Child Cancer Foundation Holiday Homes help overcome this barrier.

Families have opportunity to spend time together in a relaxing setting away from normal stressors. The holiday homes provide the perfect place for families to take time out and find strength to continue their journey.

Other families use the facilities to celebrate milestones or honour their deceased child.

If your family would like to book a holiday home please contact:

Melissa Walker
(03) 365 1485	mwalker@childcancer.org.nz
    </content>
  </HolidayHomes>

  <FamilyPlaces>
    <heading>Family places</heading>
    <img src="Resources/family_places.jpg" />
    <content>Family Places are a base for children and families to take time out from the hospital and to meet with other families, Child Cancer Foundation staff and volunteers in a caring private environment.  They provide a friendly place to go at any point during the child cancer journey.

These centres provide families with:

• Play/activity mornings for children and parents
• Parent Support Programmes
• Brochures and information about the Child Cancer Foundation.
• A book library with a range of children’s books and cancer related resources
• Access to DVDs to borrow and watch
• Access to the internet
• Kitchen facilities for a cup of tea
• Clothing and loan equipment

Auckland Family Place
76 Grafton Road
Grafton
Auckland
Phone: (09) 366 1270

Tauranga Family Place
56 Christopher Street
Tauranga
Phone: (07) 579 4141

Hawkes Bay Family Place
310 Orchard Road
Hastings
Phone: (06) 870 3189

Wellington Family Place
27 Riddiford Street
Newtown
Wellington
Phone: (04) 389 2620

Christchurch Family Place
Temporarily located at:
297 Russley Road (entrance off Ron Guthrey Road)
Avonhead
Christchurch
Phone: (03) 365 1485
Construction on our new Family Place will begin shortly!

Dunedin Family Place
28 London Street
Dunedin
Phone: (03) 471 7258
    </content>
  </FamilyPlaces>

  <FSC>
    <heading>Family Support Co-ordinators</heading>
    <content>Our Family Support Coordinators provide support to children and their families in hospital, at home, and in the community. They offer individual and group support, information, financial assistance, and advocacy. Our Coordinators also offer support for bereaved families. They connect similar families and provide a link to other agencies and community support groups.

If you are a family requiring support, please don't hesitate to get in contact with a Family Support Coordinator in your area.

Family Support - Auckland﻿
Janet Masina
(09) 303 9885	jmasina@childcancer.org.nz

Mary Mangan
(09) 303 9971	mmangan@childcancer.org.nz

Supriya Maharaj
(09) 303 9886	smaharaj@childcancer.org.nz

Family Support - Christchurch ﻿
Christine Graham
(03) 365 1485	cgraham@childcancer.org.nz

Diane Kerr
021 838 142	dkerr@childcancer.org.nz

Family Support - Dunedin﻿
Christine Donovan
(03) 471 7258	cdonovan@childcancer.org.nz

Volunteer Family Support - Eastern Bay of Plenty﻿﻿﻿
Debbie Horwood
027 408 8825	dhorwood@childcancer.org.nz

Family Support - Hawkes Bay﻿﻿
Shannyn Hansen
(06) 870 3189	shansen@childcancer.org.nz

Family Support - Lakes
Barb Richardson
027 533 3793	brichardson@childcancer.org.nz

Family Support - Manawatu
Bev Randall
021 891 791	brandall@childcancer.org.nz

Family Support - Northland
Abi Alger
021 856 451	aalger@childcancer.org.nz

Family Supoprt - Taranaki
Kathryn Hensley
021 525 938	khensley@childcancer.org.nz

Family Support - Tairawhiti
Cheryl Scott
027 361 7000	cscott@childcancer.org.nz

Family Support - Tauranga
Debbie Hockly
(07) 579 4107	dhockly@childcancer.org.nz

Family Support - Waikato
Raewyn Sayers
021 229 9792	rsayers@childcancer.org.nz

Family Support - Wellington
Sally Black
(04) 389 2620	sblack@childcancer.org.nz

Tracy Ward
(04) 389 2620	tward@childcancer.org.nz

Family Support Manager - Auckland and Northland
Marie Purcell
(09) 303 9977	mpurcell@childcancer.org.nz

Family Support Manager - Waikato, Lakes and Bays﻿
Robyn Cresswell
021 714 088	rcresswell@childcancer.org.nz

Family Support Manager - South Island and Central
Robin Furley
(03) 365 1485	rfurley@childcancer.org.nz
    </content>
  </FSC>

  <BeadsOfCourage>
    <heading>Beads of Courage®</heading>
    <img src="Resources/beads_of_courage.jpg" />
    <content>
      Become a Beads of Courage bead maker and help recognise the strength of children with cancer.
      The Beads of Courage® Programme depends upon two types of beads:

      1. Program Beads -  These beads are the ones that you may have seen on bead guides that correspond to specific events in treatment.
      2. Act of Courage Beads - These are the artist-made glass beads that are given to acknowledge the milestones in their treatment journey.

      Types of Act of Courage beads include:
      COURAGE BEADS
      BONE MARROW TRANSPLANT
      PARTNER IN COURAGE
      PURPLE HEART
      BUTTERFLY BEAD
      PARENT HEART

      Each bead donated by our community of glass bead artists are individually packaged and presented to the child. It is given with a card that specifies the donating artist's name.

      Child Cancer Foundation is in desperate need of bead artists as there are only a very small community of bead artists here in NZ. Only a few are currently donating beads on a regular basis.  Are you able to help us out by making some lamp worked beads for donation to the program – or even by donating any odd lamp worked beads that you have spare?  On a regular basis?

      Are you able to help us out by making some lamp worked beads for donation to the program or even by donating any odd lamp worked beads that you have spare? Ideally (and sadly) this year, we expect that we will need approximately 5000 of these handmade beads donated so that children can continue to receive one-of-a-kind beads for significant treatment milestones.

      If you have any questions or want more information 
      call our coordinator Kari on (09) 416 5624.

      If you are willing to contribute your beads to Beads of Courage program, please send them to:
      
      Kari Lindsay-Beale
      5 Dene Court Lane
      Greenhithe 0632
      Auckland
    </content>
  </BeadsOfCourage>
</pages>